=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 8=
=الحلقة 8=
What's that sound?
ما هذا الصوت؟
Someone is here.
هناك شخص هنا.
Check here.
انقر هنا.
Outside...
الخارج...
No one here.
لا أحد هنا.
No one here either.
لا يوجد أحد هنا أيضًا.
Boss, does K really live here?
يا رئيس، هل يعيش K هنا حقًا؟
(They found this place so quickly.)
(لقد وجدوا هذا المكان بسرعة كبيرة.)
If he hadn't gone to the hospital for that woman,
لو لم يذهب إلى المستشفى من أجل تلك المرأة،
I wouldn't have found him.
لم أكن لأجده.
Boss, no one is inside
يا رئيس، لا يوجد أحد بالداخل
and outside either.
وخارجها أيضًا.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
They're still hiding here.
ما زالوا مختبئين هنا.
Tear the place apart if you have to.
مزق المكان إذا كان عليك ذلك.
Search again.
ابحث مرة أخرى.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Take this chip.
خذ هذه الشريحة.
Don't come out no matter what happens.
لا تخرج مهما حدث.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll be fine.
سوف أكون بخير.
Give me the chip.
أعطني الشريحة.
Or I'll kill you.
أو سأقتلك.
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
you'll never get the chip back.
لن تستعيد الشريحة أبدًا.
If you don't hand it over now,
إذا لم تقم بتسليمها الآن،
you'll die.
سوف تموت.
Stop!
قف!
It's you.
إنه أنت.
Isn't this what you want?
أليس هذا ما تريد؟
Let us go.
دعونا نذهب.
You can have it.
يمكنك الحصول عليه.
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
Give me the chip. Now!
أعطني الشريحة الآن!
Look for it on your hands and knees.
ابحث عنه على يديك وركبتيك.
Where are they?
أين هم؟
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Your wound reopened.
جرحك انفتح من جديد.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Where's the chip?
أين الشريحة؟
Is it that important?
هل هو مهم لهذه الدرجة؟
You're risking your life.
أنت تخاطر بحياتك.
It is.
إنها.
It's more important than my life.
إنه أكثر أهمية من حياتي.
We won't escape together.
لن نهرب معًا.
Follow this path to get out.
اتبع هذا المسار للخروج.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
I'll get help to save you.
سأحصل على المساعدة لإنقاذك.
K, you're the mole.
ك، أنت الخلد.
I'll chop off your hands and feet.
سأقطع يديك وقدميك.
You've been exposed.
لقد تم الكشف عنك.
We have to abandon you.
علينا أن نتخلى عنك.
Don't leave me.
لا تتركنى.
You betrayed me.
لقد خنتني.
Just die.
فقط مت.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
You're running a fever.
أنت تعاني من الحمى.
Didn't I tell you to leave?
ألم أقل لك أن ترحل؟
Why did you come back?
لماذا عدت؟
Stop.
قف.
Trying to leave now.
أحاول المغادرة الآن.
Isn't it too late?
أليس الوقت متأخرا؟
I'm a drug dealer.
أنا تاجر مخدرات.
Why did you save me?
لماذا انقذتني؟
Answer me.
يجيبني.
Because I'm a doctor.
لأني طبيب.
You're lying.
أنت تكذب
I'm not.
انا لست كذلك.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
♪I smile to hide the sorrows♪
♪أبتسم لإخفاء الأحزان♪
♪How long must regrets linger♪
♪إلى متى يجب أن تستمر الندمات؟♪
♪I calmly resist♪
♪أقاوم بهدوء♪
♪The loneliness when memories swarm♪
♪الوحدة عندما تتجمع الذكريات♪
♪But time often♪
♪ولكن الوقت في كثير من الأحيان♪
♪Makes me anxious♪
♪يجعلني أشعر بالقلق♪
♪A breeze chills my skin♪
♪نسيمة تبرد بشرتي♪
♪I weep while missing the past♪
♪أبكي وأنا أفتقد الماضي♪
♪Suppressing the urge to see you♪
♪قمع الرغبة في رؤيتك♪
♪Tears run wild♪
♪الدموع تنهمر بغزارة♪
Why?
لماذا؟
Why didn't you keep pushing me away?
لماذا لم تستمر في دفعي بعيدًا؟
Didn't I warn you
ألم أحذرك؟
not to develop any feelings for me?
لا تتطور أي مشاعر تجاهي؟
Enough! I don't need you to remind me over and over.
كفى! لا أحتاج منك أن تذكرني مراراً وتكراراً.
Even if I have feelings for you,
حتى لو كان لدي مشاعر تجاهك،
we could never be together.
لن نتمكن من أن نكون معًا أبدًا.
Satisfied now?
راضي الآن؟
Good.
جيد.
Remember what you said today.
تذكر ما قلته اليوم.
Boss, there's a firelight over there.
يا رئيس، هناك ضوء نار هناك.
Stop!
قف!
Hurry.
عجل.
Keep running. Let's see where you can run to.
استمر بالركض. لنرَ إلى أين يمكنك الركض.
Search them.
ابحث عنهم.
Yes.
نعم.
Stop!
قف!
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Where's the chip?
أين الشريحة؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
Won't talk, huh?
لن تتحدث، أليس كذلك؟
K.
ك.
You're the first person to make me
أنت أول شخص يجعلني
a complete fool.
أحمق تماما.
I finally remember where I saw you.
وأخيرًا أتذكر أين رأيتك.
You're the daughter of the dean I killed.
أنت ابنة العميد الذي قتلته.
Aren't you?
أليس كذلك؟
Why did you kill her?
لماذا قتلتها؟
You want to know?
هل تريد أن تعرف؟
Go ask him.
اذهب واسأله.
Hand over the chip.
سلم الشريحة.
Or I'll push her into the sea.
أو سأدفعها إلى البحر.
Wait.
انتظر.
Her life or death means nothing to me.
حياتها أو موتها لا يعنيان شيئا بالنسبة لي.
You are really heartless.
أنت حقا بلا قلب.
I thought she'd be different for you.
اعتقدت أنها ستكون مختلفة بالنسبة لك.
Fine, I'll push her then.
حسناً، سأدفعها إذن.
I'll count to three.
سأحسب إلى ثلاثة.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Stop!
قف!
Tell me.
أخبرني.
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪